So similarly buying
is possible in Axis Bank, you will see a target of ₹800 with a stoppage of ₹769
in Axis Bank and
yesterday
Tech Mahindra has taken out a trade above the depositing average,
so buy here also
with a stoppage of ₹1000 74 for a target of ₹1120,
very good moves are being made in both Axis and Tech Mahindra yesterday,
the
traction is also there today, both these stocks alone are
on your screen as preferred picks,
now I don't know how big an event is
coming these days, today is Friday,
Anant Chaturdashi, today is the day of Ganesh Visarjan,
like mentioning the rate decisions of ECB,
Powell's speech in zero, in between that we have to
react to that market reality, China's inflation
print was to come today, that has come and the
expectation was of the best.  2.8%
expected 2.5% has come I will
discuss this further in the next show today there is a
euro
summit emergency meeting
extraordinary now in it it is being said that
preparations are being made for discussion on the gas price cap and add on to the date the
visa facilitation agreement of the eurozone with Russia is
also being prepared to be cancelled so
today's extra on de
re meeting is very important many FMC members, members of the
federation, governors who are George sahab
Christopher Joe Bowler sahab behind all of them today there
is a line up of
Ambuja Cement X the timeline of the open offer the
share tendering period is going to
end today the
Dani group of both the stocks that is the acquirer reason
today the last date of the open offer is being said today the
details of the Pillai scheme of mobile handsets will come out prediction
technology like place to Rakhi
accident etc I am going this much
our forex data is to come on your screen
Russia's GDP is to come today good
Brahmastra part van Shiva  It is going to release today, are you going to
watch it at Mines Sea Can? Oh, there is
no such plan at all, not at all,
this whole Bollywood hope ride is going on,
Manas is absolutely serious, we will keep
talking about it further,
Central Vistar Avenue which was graded 9 yesterday by the PM is
opening for the public from today
and I am leaving with a teaser, I mean
today it was the same, the teaser launch of Rath Prabhu's Yashoda movie which is
coming, when
Samantha Prabhu will
return then the direct deal will start, Namaskar
[Music]